# Chanyu Choung

Mamaroneck, NY → chanyuabc@gmail.com → (914) 575-8597 github.com/cchanyu → linkedin.com/in/chanyu-c/

A Software Engineer with entry-level experience in specializing web application development using React.js. Highly motivated programmer with a strong work ethic and a passion for software development.

## **EDUCATION**

# Lehman College, Bronx, NY

05/2023

Summa Cum Laude, GPA 3.87
Bachelor of Science, Double Majors
Computer Science, Computer Graphics and Imaging

## **SKILLS**

Programming Languages: Javascript, React.js, Node, Firebase, LuaU, Python Graphic Design: Photoshop, AfterEffect, Cinema4D, Animate, Figma, Spline

## **CERTIFICATE**

Associate Cloud Engineer (Google Cloud)

02/2023

## **LANGUAGE**

Korean (Native), English (Fluent)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Hudson's Bay Company - Saks OFF 5th Tech, New York, NY

01/2020 - 05/2020

Software Engineer

- Completed an internal employee's website
- Worked as a front-end developer using React.js
- Created specific components based on wireframes given by UI team members

## **CUNY 2x TECH - Tech Talent Pipeline, Bronx, NY**

09/2019 - 01/2020

Software Engineer

- Completed 5-months bootcamp covering the basics of web development
- Hands-on coding projects using APIs and React.js

# **PROJECTS**

# Lehman College - A.I. Research, Bronx, NY

05/2022 - 12/2022

Undergrad. Researcher

- A.I. Research under Professor Liang Zhao
- Summer Research: Explored the topic of A.I. Fairness and simulated the delayed impact
- Fall Research: Explored the topic of CNN Architectures and replicated DeepDream

#### S&J Games - Love & Law, Bronx, NY

11/2021 - 12/2022

Game Developer

- Created a 2D Visual Novel game with Ren.py
- Added in-game events or features to the Visual Novel

#### **Roblox Community, Remote**

05/2020 - 06/2021

Group Game Developer

- Created objects or components that could be reused
- Showcase: Players can try out and buy clothes in the shop or explore the map
- Obbies: Players have to beat obstacle courses as a challenge